export const questions = [
    {
        numb: 1
        question: "Who is the creator of ‘The Simpsons’?",
        answer: "D. Matt Groening",
        options: [
            "A. Trey Parker and Matt Stone",
            "B. Seth MacFarlane",
            "C. Hanna-Barbera",
            "D. Matt Groening",
        ]

    },

    {
        numb: 2
        question: "What is the name of the clown who hosts a children’s television show in Springfield?",
        answer: "B. Krusty the Clown",
        options: [
            "A. Pennywise",
            "B. Krusty the Clown",
            "C. Ronald McDonald",
            "D. Bozo the Clown",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3
        question: "Who shot Mr. Burns?",
        answer: "A. Maggie Simpson",
        options: [
            "A. Maggie Simpson",
            "B. Bart Simpson",
            "C. Homer Simpson",
            "D. Mrs. Krabappel",
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 4
        question: "Which Springfield resident has a twin brother named Herb?",
        answer: "C. Homer Simpson",
        options: [
            "A. Ned Flanders",
            "B. Moe",
            "C. Homer Simpson",
            "D. Sideshow Bob",
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 5
        question: "Who voices Moe in The Simpson?",
        answer: "B. Hank Azaria",
        options: [
            "A. Christopher Collins",
            "B. Hank Azaria",
            "C. Robert Downey Jr.",
            "D. Chris Evans",
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 6
        question: "Who is the teacher of Bart’s class at Springfield Elementary?",
        answer: "D. Mrs. Krabappel",
        options: [
            "A. Mrs. Vanderbilt",
            "B. Miss Hoover",
            "C. Mrs. Glick",
            "D. Mrs. Krabappel",
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 7
        question: "What is the name of the school bus driver?",
        answer: "A. Otto Mann",
        options: [
            "A. Otto Mann",
            "B. Barney Gumble",
            "C. Kent Brockman",
            "D.Troy McClure",
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 8
        question: "What instrument does Lisa play in her school band?",
        answer: "B. Saxophone",
        options: [
            "A. Clarinet",
            "B. Saxophone",
            "C. Flute",
            "D. Trombone",
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 9
        question: "What is the name of the elephant Bart wins in a radio contest?",
        answer: "C. Stampy",
        options: [
            "A. Trunky",
            "B. Jumbo",
            "C. Stampy",
            "D. Horton",
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 10
        question: "In Season 6, Homer joins an ancient secret society called what?",
        answer: "D. The Stonecutters",
        options: [
            "A. The Freemasons",
            "B. The Illuminati",
            "C. The Knights Templar",
            "D. The Stonecutters",
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 11
        question: "What is the name of the bowling instructor Marge develops a crush on?",
        answer: "A. Jacques",
        options: [
            "A. Jacques",
            "B. Lionel",
            "C. Francois",
            "D. Jean",
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 12
        question: "Which character is obsessed with getting revenge on Bart?",
        answer: "B. Sideshow Bob",
        options: [
            "A. Krusty the Clown",
            "B. Sideshow Bob",
            "C. Fat Tony",
            "D. Nelson Muntz",
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 13
        question: "What is the full name of Moe, the owner of Moe’s Tavern?",
        answer: "C. Moe Szyslak",
        options: [
            "A. Moe Slovak",
            "B. Moe Sawicki",
            "C. Moe Szyslak",
            "D. Moe Sadowski",
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 14
        question: "What is the vehicle Homer designs called?",
        answer: "D. The Homer",
        options: [
            "A. The Buzzwagon",
            "B. Convert-a-Car",
            "C. Turbo Donut",
            "D. The Homer",
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 15
        question: "In which season did Ralph Wiggum first appear?",
        answer: "A. Season 1",
        options: [
            "A. Season 1",
            "B. Season 2",
            "C. Season 3",
            "D. Season 4",
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 16
        question: "Which pop artist’s Super Bowl show was predicted in ‘The Simpsons’?",
        answer: "A. Lady Gaga",
        options: [
            "A. Lady Gaga",
            "B. Janet Jackson",
            "C. Madonna",
            "D. Beyoncé",
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 17
        question: "What is Springfield’s local newspaper called?",
        answer: "B. The Springfield Shopper",
        options: [
            "A. The Springfield Times",
            "B. The Springfield Shopper",
            "C. The Springfield Post",
            "D. The Springfield Journal",
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 18
        question: "Which acclaimed physicist made a guest appearance as himself?",
        answer: "C. Stephen Hawking",
        options: [
            "A. Alan Guth",
            "B. Peter Higgs",
            "C. Stephen Hawking",
            "D. Edward Witten",
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 19
        question: "Who voiced Bart’s girlfriend Jessica?",
        answer: "C. Meryl Streep",
        options: [
            "A. Goldie Hawn",
            "B. Helen Mirren",
            "C. Meryl Streep",
            "D. Emma Thompson",
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 20
        question: "In what year did The Simpsons first air?",
        answer: "B. 1989",
        options: [
            "A. 1987",
            "B. 1989",
            "C. 1990",
            "D. 1992",
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 21
        question: "What fruit does Homer build out of ham cubes?",
        answer: "B. Apple",
        options: [
            "A. Pineapple",
            "B. Apple",
            "C. Orange",
            "D. Mango",
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 22
        question: "Bart and Milhouse’s favourite comic book character is known as what?",
        answer: "D. Radioactive Man",
        options: [
            "A. Bumblebee Man",
            "B. Batman",
            "C. Spiderman",
            "D. Radioactive Man",
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 23
        question: "What is the secret ingredient in the Flaming Moe cocktail?",
        answer: "C. Cough syrup",
        options: [
            "A. Golden syrup",
            "B. Maple syrup",
            "C. Cough syrup",
            "D. Mouthwash",
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 24
        question: "What is the name of Ned Flanders’s first wife?",
        answer: "B. Maude",
        options: [
            "A. Martha",
            "B. Maude",
            "C. Madison",
            "D. Mildred",
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 25
        question: "What is the name of the amusement park in Springfield?",
        answer: "D. Krustyland",
        options: [
            "A. Scratchyland",
            "B. Homerland",
            "C. Neverland",
            "D. Krustyland",
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 26
        question: "Which character’s catchphrase is “Ha-Ha!”?",
        answer: "A. Nelson Muntz",
        options: [
            "A. Nelson Muntz",
            "B. Squeaky-Voiced Teen",
            "C. Ralph Wiggum",
            "D. Grampa Simpson",
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 27
        question: "Which store is located right next to Moe’s Tavern?",
        answer: "C. King Toot’s Music Store",
        options: [
            "A. Kwik-E-Mart",
            "B. Lard Lad Donuts",
            "C. King Toot’s Music Store",
            "D. The Leftorium",
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 28
        question: "Who is the leader of the infamous Springfield Mafia?",
        answer: "A. Fat Tony",
        options: [
            "A. Fat Tony",
            "B. Luigi Risotto",
            "C. Frankie the Squealer",
            "D. Johnny Tightlips",
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 29
        question: "What is the name of Springfield’s resident news anchor?",
        answer: "B. Kent Brockman",
        options: [
            "A. Brent Stockman",
            "B. Kent Brockman",
            "C. Godfrey Jones",
            "D. Krusty the Clown",
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 30
        question: "In what year was ‘The Simpsons Movie’ released?",
        answer: "C. 2007",
        options: [
            "A. 2004",
            "B. 2005",
            "C. 2007",
            "D. 2008",
        ]
    ];


















